Boxbusters!
If there’s something strange
In your videogame
Who you gonna call?
Boxbusters!
If there’s something weird
And it don’t look good
Who you gonna call?
Boxbusters!
I ain’t afraid of no bug!
I ain’t afraid of no glitch!
If you’re seeing things
Running through your code
Who can you call?
Boxbusters!
An invisible wall
That you just can’t pass
Oh, who you gonna call?
Boxbusters!
I ain’t afraid of no bug!
I ain’t afraid of no glitch!
Who you gonna call?
Boxbusters!
If you’ve got a bug
Debug the code!
And build!
Boxbusters!
I ain’t afraid of no bug!
I hear it likes the devs!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Who you gonna call?
Boxbusters!
Mmm, if you've had a dose
Of a freaky bug baby
You better call
Boxbusters!
Let me tell you something
Busting makes the feature!
I ain’t afraid of no bug!
I ain’t afraid of no glitch!
Don't leave your code alone, oh no!
Boxbusters!
When he appears through your code…
Unless you just a want some more!
I think you better call
Boxbusters!
Who you gonna call?
Ah, think you better call...
Boxbusters!
Who you gonna call?
I can't hear you!
Boxbusters!
Louder!
Who you gonna call?
Boxbusters!
Who can you call?
Who you gonna call?
Boxbusters!